It was filmed in 6 days for 25 thousand dollars. The government didn't want you to see it. It was banned in 23 states.
It has grossed over 600 million dollars. And it is the most profitable film in motion picture history.
Inside Deep Throat is a documentary film directed by Randy Barbato.
In 1972, a seemingly typical shoestring budget pornographic film was made
in a Florida hotel: "Deep Throat," starring Linda Lovelace.
This film would surpass the wildest expectation of everyone involved to
become one of the most successful independent films of all time.
It caught the public imagination which met the spirit of the times, even as the self-appointed guardians of public morality struggled to
suppress it, and created, for a brief moment, a possible future where sexuality in film had a bold artistic potential.
This film covers the story of the making of this controversial film, its stunning success, its hysterical opposition
along with its dark side of mob influence and allegations of the on set mistreatment of the film's star.
Narrator (voice), played by Dennis Hopper.
Self, played by Peter Bart.
Self (archive footage), played by Warren Beatty.
Self, played by Carl Bernstein.
Self, played by Norman Mailer.
Self, played by John Waters.
Inside Deep Throat is a 2005 American documentary film about the 1972 pornographic film Deep
Throat, at the forefront of the Golden Age of Porn, and its effects on American society.
The film explores themes of pornography, 1970s, sexual revolution.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.